pro-market.net 2005-03-23

# :: AlmondNet - Privacy Policy ::

AlmondNet is a New York-based interactive advertising technology company that has developed a system which enables for the targeting of ads based on any combination of audience attributes (registration, behavioral, demographic, etc.). 

The ads are presented either by AlmondNet on sites where it buys media or by clients of AlmondNet that use the company’s outsourced system within their own sites. In either case the AlmondNet system does NOT collect personal identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, social security number or e-mail.

**What does this Privacy Policy Cover?**

The following Privacy Policy relates to AlmondNet’s usage of its system. This Privacy Policy covers how AlmondNet treats information that it collects and receives. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that AlmondNet does not own or control or to people that AlmondNet does not employ or manage.  AlmondNet clients’ usage of the company’s outsourced system is subjected to their own privacy policies.

**What kind of information is collected and how is it used ?**

AlmondNet does NOT collect any personal identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number, social security number or e-mail.

AlmondNet may collect the following information:

·         The phrase searched by a visitor to a search engine

·         The search made by a visitor to a travel site or any other site

·         The content viewed by a visitor to a certain section or a certain site

AlmondNet does NOT collect any adult related searches or site visits.

The information is collected ANONYMOUSLY by using anonymous cookies in order to correlate the collected information with a specific computer’s browser, which AlmondNet placed a cookie on.

The AlmondNet cookie is a small computer file that can be read only by the AlmondNet system and that informs the AlmondNet system that it has already encountered this computer in the past and that this computer was either used in the last 30 days to search for a certain phrase (such as for ‘car insurance’), product or service or used in the last 30 days to visit a certain section or site. 

Since AlmondNet does not collect personal identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone or e-mail) it has no way of knowing, which of the hundreds of millions of people that surf the web does this computer belong to. 

The only thing AlmondNet can do – on sites where it has access to ad space – if it happens to encounter a computer it has already encountered in the last 30 days – it can serve that computer an ad relevant to the recent search or content viewed by this computer.

**With whom is the information shared?**

AlmondNet shares the anonymous collected information with no one.

AlmondNet may grant advertising companies or ad space owners with access to reports that aggregate information about the ads presented by the AlmondNet system. It should be emphasized that the reports are not and could not be connected to individual users. 

**What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under AlmondNet control?**

All information collected by the AlmondNet system is stored in databases that are stored in a secure data center.  Both physical and Internet access is strictly protected and limited.  Access is granted only to those with authorization. The information is stored anonymously, and is therefore not personally identifiable – even by AlmondNet Inc.

**How can I opt-out?**

If you would like to opt-out from viewing ads relevant to recent **non-personally identifiable** searches and site visits you made, please click HERE:

OPT-OUT

This will place an AlmondNet cookie on your computer that will inform AlmondNet NOT to collect non-personal identifiable information about you or to present you with ads. 

Please note that if you choose to opt-out, then in the following circumstances you will be required to renew your opt-out choice: 

·         Change of a computer

·         Change of a browser

·         Deleting the opt-out cookie

**How are changes to the AlmondNet Privacy Policy made ?**

AlmondNet publishes its privacy policy on its web site at www.almondnet.com. Any material change to AlmondNet’s privacy policy will be prominently noted in the published policy. In addition, you may contact AlmondNet with any question or concern you may have at:

                               AlmondNet, Inc.

                               134 Spring Street, Suite 302

                               New York, NY 10012

                               Tel:  212-219-5070

                               Fax: 212-219-5149

                               E-mail: [info@almondnet.com](mailto:info@almondnet.com)
